<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Danganronpa MK2</title>
    <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Danganronpa MK2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sozzay.com/MK2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 11</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-11/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   I’ve seen so many ridiculous things on this island... But this... this puts everything else to shame.  PROLOGUE   Huh...huh...?  PROLOGUE   H...How did those statues just...!?  PROLOGUE   They’re not statues! They’re Monobeasts!  PROLOGUE   M...MONSTEEEEEEEEEERS!!!  PROLOGUE   No, I just said they’re Monobeasts!  PROLOGUE   At that moment, I should have been terrified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 10</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-10/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   W-Where are you?! Where are you hiding!?Why are you yelling? What’s going on!?Hey! Show yourself!Show yourself?U-Usami, who are you talking to?  PROLOGUE   Puhuhuhu!...Huh?Ahhhh-hahahahahahaha!  PROLOGUE   Why, hello there! Thank you all for waiting!Long time, no see guys!I am Monokuma! I’m the headmaster of this academy!  PROLOGUE   Ahem, now that I have made my dashing appearance, the first thing I need to say is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 9</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-9/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Anyway, Usami! What&#39;s this present you mentioned in your announcement earlier?  PROLOGUE   Ah, that&#39;s right! Well, of course I didn&#39;t forget...  PROLOGUE   Love! Love! This is it! Don&#39;t be upset! I&#39;ve prepared one for you all, so don&#39;t worry!  PROLOGUE   ...What is this...?  PROLOGUE   Pfft, teehee! It&#39;s an Usami Strap! If you squeeze the tummy, it talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 8</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-8/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Mahiru... it looks like if we cross that bridge, we’ll reach another island not far from here.Another island... Do you think it’s safe?I can’t say. I’ve yet to explore it.Well, I guess we can check it out ourselves...But, you better have a backup plan in case things go wrong!While I’m sure there’s nothing to fear... I’ll think up a plan B, just for you.So he wouldn’t bother if I wasn’t here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-7/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Oh... it’s a restaurant.  PROLOGUE   It’s enormous. We could easily hold a banquet here. It kind of has this tropical, open country feeling.Open? You realise we’re trapped on an island, right?  PROLOGUE   Are we really trapped...?Are you for real? What else could it be!?  PROLOGUE   ............Oh well. We can talk about it after we’ve finished introducing ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-6/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Huh... Compared to the weirdos I’ve met so far, this guy looks pretty normal.Hey, you... We haven’t introduced ourselves, have we?  PROLOGUE   Yeah... we haven’t.By the way, aren’t you the girl who fainted on the beach?Did you really have to remind me?  PROLOGUE   Sorry, I just wanted to see if you were okay.“Okay?” Jeez... I’ll be okay when I’m off this island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-5/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Peeking, peeking...  PROLOGUE   Oh haiiiiiiiiiii! I don’t know you!Um... hello. My name is Mahiru Koizumi, and-  PROLOGUE   Hellooooo? Your tension is super low! Are you feeling alright?Ah, that&#39;s right! Introductions are a go-go!  PROLOGUE   &#34;I,&#34; &#34;Buki,&#34; &#34;Mio,&#34; &#34;Da!&#34; Put it together and what do you get? Ibuki Mioda!   PROLOGUE   Ibuki Mioda? I swear I know that name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-4/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Ah! This is an airport, isn’t it? And... are those......Airplanes!?Those are airplanes! Does this mean we can fly off of this island!?  PROLOGUE   Pains me to say, but... ‘fraid not.If they were damaged, I could fix &#39;em, but it looks like these planes are just for show...Huh? Just for show?  PROLOGUE   The engines have been completely removed. I can do a lot of things, but.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-3/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Hey...Can you hear me...?  PROLOGUE   Hey, are you alright?...You seem pretty out of it.To be honest, I’m also... No, everyone else feels the same, too............Hey, are you listening?........  PROLOGUE   Hey, are you sure you&#39;re okay?Ah... I think so...  PROLOGUE   Alright, I’m glad.........  PROLOGUE   Golden sand... blue sea...Strong, bright sunlight blazing down... and a gentle sea breeze caressing my skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-2/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   What...is that...?I... I think it’s a stuffed animal... That’s right, I am a squeezably soft stuffed animal.“Magical Miracle Girl ★ Usami”... A.K.A. Usami!I may not look like it, but I am your squeezably soft teacher.Nice to meet you all!  PROLOGUE   H-Huh? Am I hallucinating? Am I the only one who&#39;s seeing this?  PROLOGUE   Nah, I see it too...  PROLOGUE   What&#39;s with this talkin&#39; Chihuahua!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-1/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   That day wasn’t just another regular day for me.No... it was more nerve-wracking than I could have ever anticipated.  PROLOGUE   The reality of the situation didn’t set in until I was actually standing in front of the building.Adrenaline began to rush through me, as if I was committing a horrible crime.Something... completely unlike transferring to a new school.  PROLOGUE   Then again, people have always told me this schoolis far from ordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/credits/</guid>
      <description>CREATORSSozzayTwitter - @SozzayDRTumblr - sozzayBitesizeBirdTwitter - @BitesizeBirdINSPIRED BYorenronenFPzeroWEBSITE BYBamboshTwitter - @BamboshuARTISTSMidDinosTwitter - @MidDinosNevaloneReddit - u/Neva-neva-LoveEDITORSRebusDiscord - Rebus #0516MagilouDiscord - ℳagιloυ ★#4706Andrea BandreaTwitter - @officiallilith2JadecoreTumblr - jadecoreAnonymous AceMojo LecroweTwitter - @MojoLecroweVASpectrehouseTwitter - @spectrehouseNozoCubeyTwitter - @cubey101LoafGatrTwitter - @madnesshank If you think you are missing from the credits, please contact Sozzay on Tumblr or Twitter!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
