<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chapter 1 on Danganronpa MK2</title>
    <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/tags/chapter-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chapter 1 on Danganronpa MK2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sozzay.com/MK2/tags/chapter-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-5/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Um...Uwa!It looked like you guys were arguing...so I wasn&#39;t sure when to actually show up... It looks like I showed up at an awkward time!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Why... are you dressed like that?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Oh, didn&#39;t I mention it in my recent broadcast? It&#39;s my costume for the fun time!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Oh, don&#39;t tell me you&#39;re going to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-4/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ....It’d be boring to just remain in my room...There’s plenty of time left in the day. Maybe I should spend it with someone...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Byakuya is very reliable. As expected of the Ultimate Affluent Progeny.With everyone working together under such a splendid leader, we&#39;ll be able to overcome any difficulty!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Then let&#39;s do what we can, just as our leader ordered us to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-3/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Eh!? Whatis thatthing!?T-This... wasn’t here when we came to the park before, was it!?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   No...I&#39;m pretty sure it wasn&#39;t!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I found it this morning...when I was exploring the island one more time. It&#39;s unknown...when it was actually placed here...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Monokuma must have placed this object...   CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   It looks like a clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-2/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   You’re late, you two.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Huh? What’s the matter with Kazuichi?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Sniff...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Kyahaha! Even though you look all flashy, you&#39;re actually a big coward!Are you gonna be okaaaay? People like you are usually the first victim, you know?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   N... No they aren’t! Don’t say stuff like that!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Anyway, Byakuya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-1/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1
A MOST DESPAIR FILLED GAME  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   This... this is unbelievable. Someone’s got to be pulling my leg here.Maybe it’s me. Maybe this is all one big demented dream.If it is, I’d do anything to wake up right now.As I triedto put my fragmented thoughts into words, something trickled down my spine.A familiar tingling sensation......Goosebumps. There were goosebumps all over my body.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I switch off the tablet and look up from where I’m sitting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
