<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>all updates on Danganronpa MK2</title>
    <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/tags/all-updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in all updates on Danganronpa MK2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sozzay.com/MK2/tags/all-updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 10</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-10/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Thank you for waiting.Teruteru is in the kitchen, and... it appears Fuyuhiko did not come.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I apologize. I did inform him about the party, but...Hey, you don’t need to apologize. It&#39;s his fault for not coming...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I explicitly stated that attendance was mandatory, but...It&#39;s fine... If just one person is absent, that shouldn&#39;t pose a problem....He won&#39;t be able to do anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 9</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-9/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   *Ding dong Bing bong*  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   This is an announcement from Hope’s Peak Academy’s Field Trip Executive Committee...It is now 10pm.Please rest peacefully, along with the soothing sound of the waves.Well then, pleasant dreams. Goodnight...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Right... So I’m supposed to be going to the old building, aren’t I?The moments before a party are arguably the most exciting, anticipation being greater than the event and all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 8</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-8/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Unusually, Chiaki wasn&#39;t playing any games.Um, how are you Chiaki?.......Good.O-Okay....  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   You want to hang out?I guess we could play some games together. You know how to play the games here, right?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Chiaki showed me how to play some of the games in the lobby. It quickly became apparent why she’s called the UltimateGamer...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Chiaki and I grew a little closer today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-7/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   When I entered the restaurant, I found several people already waiting inside.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Everyone looked exhausted... It seems I wasn’t alone in having a rough night’s sleep.Not wanting to disturb anyone, I quietly took to a corner of the restaurant and waited for the others to arrive.   CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-6/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   *Ding dong Bing bong*  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Ahem... Hope&#39;s Peak Academy&#39;s School Trip Executive Committee has an announcement to make...Gooooood morning, everyone! Looks like today is gonna be another perfect, tropical day!Now then, let&#39;s show some enthusiasm and make sure to give it our all today!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Ah.I sat up in my bed, my head still throbbing from yesterday.I’d tossedand turned all night, unable to think of anything except last night’s events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-5/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Um...Uwa!It looked like you guys were arguing...so I wasn&#39;t sure when to actually show up... It looks like I showed up at an awkward time!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Why... are you dressed like that?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Oh, didn&#39;t I mention it in my recent broadcast? It&#39;s my costume for the fun time!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Oh, don&#39;t tell me you&#39;re going to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-4/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ....It’d be boring to just remain in my room...There’s plenty of time left in the day. Maybe I should spend it with someone...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Byakuya is very reliable. As expected of the Ultimate Affluent Progeny.With everyone working together under such a splendid leader, we&#39;ll be able to overcome any difficulty!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Then let&#39;s do what we can, just as our leader ordered us to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-3/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   ...Eh!? Whatis thatthing!?T-This... wasn’t here when we came to the park before, was it!?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   No...I&#39;m pretty sure it wasn&#39;t!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I found it this morning...when I was exploring the island one more time. It&#39;s unknown...when it was actually placed here...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Monokuma must have placed this object...   CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   It looks like a clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-2/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   You’re late, you two.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Huh? What’s the matter with Kazuichi?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Sniff...  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Kyahaha! Even though you look all flashy, you&#39;re actually a big coward!Are you gonna be okaaaay? People like you are usually the first victim, you know?  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   N... No they aren’t! Don’t say stuff like that!  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   Anyway, Byakuya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/1-1/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1
A MOST DESPAIR FILLED GAME  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   This... this is unbelievable. Someone’s got to be pulling my leg here.Maybe it’s me. Maybe this is all one big demented dream.If it is, I’d do anything to wake up right now.As I triedto put my fragmented thoughts into words, something trickled down my spine.A familiar tingling sensation......Goosebumps. There were goosebumps all over my body.  CHAPTER&amp;nbsp;01   I switch off the tablet and look up from where I’m sitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 11</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-11/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   I’ve seen so many ridiculous things on this island... But this... this puts everything else to shame.  PROLOGUE   Huh...huh...?  PROLOGUE   H...How did those statues just...!?  PROLOGUE   They’re not statues! They’re Monobeasts!  PROLOGUE   M...MONSTEEEEEEEEEERS!!!  PROLOGUE   No, I just said they’re Monobeasts!  PROLOGUE   At that moment, I should have been terrified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 10</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-10/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   W-Where are you?! Where are you hiding!?Why are you yelling? What’s going on!?Hey! Show yourself!Show yourself?U-Usami, who are you talking to?  PROLOGUE   Puhuhuhu!...Huh?Ahhhh-hahahahahahaha!  PROLOGUE   Why, hello there! Thank you all for waiting!Long time, no see guys!I am Monokuma! I’m the headmaster of this academy!  PROLOGUE   Ahem, now that I have made my dashing appearance, the first thing I need to say is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 9</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-9/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Anyway, Usami! What&#39;s this present you mentioned in your announcement earlier?  PROLOGUE   Ah, that&#39;s right! Well, of course I didn&#39;t forget...  PROLOGUE   Love! Love! This is it! Don&#39;t be upset! I&#39;ve prepared one for you all, so don&#39;t worry!  PROLOGUE   ...What is this...?  PROLOGUE   Pfft, teehee! It&#39;s an Usami Strap! If you squeeze the tummy, it talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 8</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-8/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Mahiru... it looks like if we cross that bridge, we’ll reach another island not far from here.Another island... Do you think it’s safe?I can’t say. I’ve yet to explore it.Well, I guess we can check it out ourselves...But, you better have a backup plan in case things go wrong!While I’m sure there’s nothing to fear... I’ll think up a plan B, just for you.So he wouldn’t bother if I wasn’t here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-7/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Oh... it’s a restaurant.  PROLOGUE   It’s enormous. We could easily hold a banquet here. It kind of has this tropical, open country feeling.Open? You realise we’re trapped on an island, right?  PROLOGUE   Are we really trapped...?Are you for real? What else could it be!?  PROLOGUE   ............Oh well. We can talk about it after we’ve finished introducing ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-6/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Huh... Compared to the weirdos I’ve met so far, this guy looks pretty normal.Hey, you... We haven’t introduced ourselves, have we?  PROLOGUE   Yeah... we haven’t.By the way, aren’t you the girl who fainted on the beach?Did you really have to remind me?  PROLOGUE   Sorry, I just wanted to see if you were okay.“Okay?” Jeez... I’ll be okay when I’m off this island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-5/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Peeking, peeking...  PROLOGUE   Oh haiiiiiiiiiii! I don’t know you!Um... hello. My name is Mahiru Koizumi, and-  PROLOGUE   Hellooooo? Your tension is super low! Are you feeling alright?Ah, that&#39;s right! Introductions are a go-go!  PROLOGUE   &#34;I,&#34; &#34;Buki,&#34; &#34;Mio,&#34; &#34;Da!&#34; Put it together and what do you get? Ibuki Mioda!   PROLOGUE   Ibuki Mioda? I swear I know that name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-4/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Ah! This is an airport, isn’t it? And... are those......Airplanes!?Those are airplanes! Does this mean we can fly off of this island!?  PROLOGUE   Pains me to say, but... ‘fraid not.If they were damaged, I could fix &#39;em, but it looks like these planes are just for show...Huh? Just for show?  PROLOGUE   The engines have been completely removed. I can do a lot of things, but.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-3/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   Hey...Can you hear me...?  PROLOGUE   Hey, are you alright?...You seem pretty out of it.To be honest, I’m also... No, everyone else feels the same, too............Hey, are you listening?........  PROLOGUE   Hey, are you sure you&#39;re okay?Ah... I think so...  PROLOGUE   Alright, I’m glad.........  PROLOGUE   Golden sand... blue sea...Strong, bright sunlight blazing down... and a gentle sea breeze caressing my skin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-2/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   What...is that...?I... I think it’s a stuffed animal... That’s right, I am a squeezably soft stuffed animal.“Magical Miracle Girl ★ Usami”... A.K.A. Usami!I may not look like it, but I am your squeezably soft teacher.Nice to meet you all!  PROLOGUE   H-Huh? Am I hallucinating? Am I the only one who&#39;s seeing this?  PROLOGUE   Nah, I see it too...  PROLOGUE   What&#39;s with this talkin&#39; Chihuahua!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sozzay.com/MK2/liveblog/prologue-1/</guid>
      <description>PROLOGUE   That day wasn’t just another regular day for me.No... it was more nerve-wracking than I could have ever anticipated.  PROLOGUE   The reality of the situation didn’t set in until I was actually standing in front of the building.Adrenaline began to rush through me, as if I was committing a horrible crime.Something... completely unlike transferring to a new school.  PROLOGUE   Then again, people have always told me this schoolis far from ordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
